alpinezone.com 2005-12-17

# AlpineZone.com Privacy Policy

|  | 

---  
 [More than 1,500 Skiers and Riders Take Advantage of a Free Powder Day at Attitash](http://news.alpinezone.com/6936/) \- Dec 16, 2005 - 4:37 PM  
  
 [Attitash Instant Winter Scratch Tickets to Hit the Mount Washington Valley](http://news.alpinezone.com/6935/) \- Dec 16, 2005 - 4:35 PM  
  
 [Crotched Mountain Opens 100% Terrain with Full Coverage](http://news.alpinezone.com/6934/) \- Dec 16, 2005 - 4:35 PM  
  
 [Catamount Skiers and Riders to Enjoy Best Early Season Conditions Ever](http://news.alpinezone.com/6891/) \- Dec 14, 2005 - 4:36 PM  
  
 [New Jersey Transit Bus Service to Mountain Creek Resumes for 2005-06 Season](http://news.alpinezone.com/6890/) \- Dec 14, 2005 - 2:27 PM  
  
 [Live Music, Rail Jam and Telemark Demos at Whiteface This Weekend](http://news.alpinezone.com/6889/) \- Dec 14, 2005 - 1:56 PM  
  
 [The Summit of Whiteface Opens for Skiing and Riding Today](http://news.alpinezone.com/6882/) \- Dec 14, 2005 - 12:56 PM  
  
 [Learn to Turn for $39 at Loon Mountain, Waterville Valley and Cranmore](http://news.alpinezone.com/6867/) \- Dec 13, 2005 - 4:30 PM  
  
 [Award Winning Safety Theme at Sunday River Encourages Guests to Go With The Flow](http://news.alpinezone.com/6866/) \- Dec 13, 2005 - 4:29 PM  
  
 [Gore Mountain Offers Fantastic Early Season](http://news.alpinezone.com/6865/) \- Dec 13, 2005 - 4:29 PM  

---  
   Dec 17, 2005 - 4:01 AM  
   by [BeanoNYC](http://forums.alpinezone.com/profile.php?mode=viewprofile&u=1195&sid=8350d6c699960aacfa6c55af69a7f318)  
  
   Dec 17, 2005 - 1:25 AM  
   by [Zand](http://forums.alpinezone.com/profile.php?mode=viewprofile&u=460&sid=8350d6c699960aacfa6c55af69a7f318)  
  
   Dec 16, 2005 - 10:51 PM  
   by [cyrk007](http://forums.alpinezone.com/profile.php?mode=viewprofile&u=1113&sid=8350d6c699960aacfa6c55af69a7f318)  
  
   Dec 16, 2005 - 10:45 PM  
   by [cyrk007](http://forums.alpinezone.com/profile.php?mode=viewprofile&u=1113&sid=8350d6c699960aacfa6c55af69a7f318)  
  
   Dec 16, 2005 - 10:38 PM  
   by [Npage148](http://forums.alpinezone.com/profile.php?mode=viewprofile&u=1332&sid=8350d6c699960aacfa6c55af69a7f318)  
  
   Dec 16, 2005 - 10:36 PM  
   by [ALLSKIING](http://forums.alpinezone.com/profile.php?mode=viewprofile&u=1105&sid=8350d6c699960aacfa6c55af69a7f318)  
  
   Dec 16, 2005 - 10:23 PM  
   by [Bumpsis](http://forums.alpinezone.com/profile.php?mode=viewprofile&u=621&sid=8350d6c699960aacfa6c55af69a7f318)  
  
   Dec 16, 2005 - 10:14 PM  
   by [Bumpsis](http://forums.alpinezone.com/profile.php?mode=viewprofile&u=621&sid=8350d6c699960aacfa6c55af69a7f318)  
  
   Dec 16, 2005 - 9:55 PM  
   by [teachski](http://forums.alpinezone.com/profile.php?mode=viewprofile&u=410&sid=8350d6c699960aacfa6c55af69a7f318)  
  
   Dec 16, 2005 - 9:28 PM  
   by [Skiiboot](http://forums.alpinezone.com/profile.php?mode=viewprofile&u=1767&sid=8350d6c699960aacfa6c55af69a7f318)  

| 

[Home](http://www.alpinezone.com/)  > ** AlpineZone.com Privacy Policy**

**Introduction:**  
We are committed to protecting your privacy at AlpineZone.com. We will not collect any personal information from you that you do not volunteer, and we are the sole owner of all information collected on this site. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way that we have not mentioned in this statement. For more information, please click one of the links below:

**Cookies  
Email  
Third parties  
AlpineZone's affiliate services  
Links  
Security  
Obtaining your consent  
Questions?**

* * *

**Cookies:**  
Like many other Web sites, AlpineZone.com uses cookies to identify members so they don't have to re-enter a username and password when they, for example, wish to post to a topic in the [Message Forums](http://forums.alpinezone.com/). Cookies also help us improve your experience and display more prominently goods and services that might interest you. If you do not have cookies enabled, you must enter your password each time you access our site's member features.

Top  

**Email:**  
There are three reasons for requesting your Email address:

  * **[E-Newsletter Subscription](http://www.alpinezone.com/newsletter.htm):** This is an opt-in newsletter which provides subscribers information we feel may interest Northeast mountain enthusiasts. We try to limit the mailing to 2-3 per month. Subscribers can unsubscribe from the E-Newsletter at any time from this [page](http://www.alpinezone.com/newsletter.htm) and each E-Newsletter mailing also has an unsubscribe link. **Subscription to the E-Newsletter is the only sales and marketing tool used to send Email regarding AlpineZone.com services or other information.**
  * **[Forum Membership](http://forums.alpinezone.com/):** You must [register](http://forums.alpinezone.com/profile.php?mode=register) to post in the AlpineZone [Message Forums](http://forums.alpinezone.com/). The registration process requires the entry of a valid Email address. There is also forum functionality that can only be achieved via a valid Email address (e.g. watched topic and private message notification). The forum software does have a mass Email capability, but it has been our policy not to use it. If you are interested in receiving Emails regarding AlpineZone.com information and services, please subscribe to the [ E-Newsletter](http://www.alpinezone.com/newsletter.htm) in conjunction with a forum membership.
  * **[Contest Entry](http://www.alpinezone.com/contest/):** At times, we run contests such as lift ticket giveaways. As part of the contest entry we need to collect personal information such as your name, forum username, Email address, mailing address, etc. This information is used to contact winners and for prize fulfillment. We do not contact contest entrants via Email for any reason not related to the contest itself. If you are interested in receiving Emails regarding AlpineZone.com information and services, please indicate you would like to join the AlpineZone.com [ E-Newsletter](http://www.alpinezone.com/newsletter.htm) when filling out the entry form.

Top  

**Third parties:**  
AlpineZone.com may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns gathered during thousands of visits to our Web site each month but does not contain behavioral or identifying information about any individual member or visitor, unless that member or visitor has given us permission to share that information. We may also provide log files and other databases of user information to third parties for analysis, so we can get a better understanding of traffic through our site and thus improve our content offerings. At times, AlpineZone.com uses a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our sites. This company may use information about your visits to our and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Top  

**AlpineZone.com's affiliate services:**  
AlpineZone.com has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with relevant vendors and service providers. Our [Gear](http://alpinezone.altrec.com/mpgate/Alpin4/shop/), [Lodging](http://lodging.alpinezone.com/) and [Merchandise](http://www.cafepress.com/alpinezone) sections are currently available through partnerships with Altrec.com, Worldres.com and CafePress.com, respectively. Their Privacy Policies are accessible below:

Top  

**Links:**  
This web site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another Web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

Top  

**Security:**  
We use reasonable precautions to keep the personal information you disclose in your browsing secure. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security.

Top

**Obtaining your consent:**  
By using our Web site, you give AlpineZone.com permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. If you register at AlpineZone.com, you authorize AlpineZone.com to use information you provide to personalize the information we deliver to you and to use your demographic information when calculating aggregate visitor data. AlpineZone.com may occasionally amend this policy. We suggest that you bookmark this page and check to see if it has changed from time to time.

Top

**Questions?**  
If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, contact:

Greg Blasko  
AlpineZone.com  
(203) 206-9147  

Top

| |
